https://www.locamoda.com/privacy/

Connect to your account
Search for:
TRENDING
chairstandstudiomoderndressersofabedroomwoodwalnutofficebedlamp
Privacy
LocaModa.com also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on LocaModa.com blogs/sites. LocaModa.com only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to LocaModa.com’s websites choose to interact with LocaModa.com in ways that require LocaModa.com to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that LocaModa.com gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at LocaModa.com to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with LocaModa.com are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, LocaModa.com collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with LocaModa.com. LocaModa.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Aggregated Statistics
LocaModa.com may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. LocaModa.com may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, LocaModa.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
LocaModa.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on LocaModa.com’s behalf or to provide services available at LocaModa.com’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using LocaModa.com’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. LocaModa.com will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, LocaModa.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when LocaModa.com believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of LocaModa.com, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an LocaModa.com website and have supplied your email address, LocaModa.com may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with LocaModa.com and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. LocaModa.com takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. LocaModa.com uses cookies to help LocaModa.com identify and track visitors, their usage of LocaModa.com website, and their website access preferences. LocaModa.com visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using LocaModa.com’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of LocaModa.com’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
Business Transfers
If LocaModa.com, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that LocaModa.com goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of LocaModa.com may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.
Ads
Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by LocaModa.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, LocaModa.com may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in LocaModa.com’s sole discretion. LocaModa.com encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a LocaModa.com account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
BE SOCIAL
Facebook
Twitter
Pinterest
Instagram
RECEIVE EMAIL UPDATES
HOT PRODUCTS
Oslo Round Bed
Terms & Conditions
© Copyright 2020 LocaModa.com.
1 Broadway, Cambridge, MA 02142
care@locamoda.com
+1 941 213 5635
WISHLIST
Login
Username or email address *
Password *
Remember me
SIGN IN
Create Account
Forgot password
Create an account
Email address *
Your personal data will be used to support your experience throughout this website, to manage access to your account, and for other purposes described in our privacy policy.
CREATE ACCOUNT
LOGIN
Forgot password
Password Recovery
Lost your password? Please enter your username or email address. You will receive a link to create a new password via email.
Username or email
RESET PASSWORD
Create Account
LOGIN
